didx.net 2011-05-30

# DIDX - DID/DDI wholesale Service Provider:- Privacy Policy

The policies below are applicable to all of Super Technologies, Inc.'s websites (parent site [www.supertec.com](http://www.supertec.com/)),further listed as Supertec.

**

  1. General Information 
  2. Security Measures
  3. Personally-Identifiable Information
  4. Non-Personally-Identifiable Information Collected Automatically
  5. Use of Cookies
  6. Declining Email Offers
  7. Who to Contact

**

**I. General**  
Supertec respects the privacy of each individual who visits its web sites, who responds to our interactive advertisements and who sends us e-mail. This Privacy Policy outlines the information Supertec will collect and how we will use that information. This Policy will instruct you on what to do if you do not want your personal information collected or shared when you visit Supertec web sites, when you respond to our Web-based advertisements or and when you send us email. 

**II. Security**  
All online order forms from Supertec make available a Secure Socket Layer (SSL) protocol to provide "secure sessions" for our visitors with "s" added after http. Through the "secure session," information that you input into a Supertec online order form will be sent and will arrive privately and unaltered at a Supertec server. This security prohibits other companies and web users from being able to access your information. 

**III. Personally-Identifiable Information**  
Supertec will not collect any personally-identifiable information about you (your name, address, telephone number, or email address) unless you provide it to us voluntarily.

The following are a few examples of when Supertec may require that you provide personally-identifiable information:

  * to complete an online order for a product or service 
  * to signup for our newsletter or other advertisements 
  * to request more information about new or current Supertec products or services 

If you do not want your personally-identifiable information collected, do not submit it to us. If you have already submitted this information and would like for us to remove it from our records, please contact us at the email address listed at the bottom of this Statement. We will use reasonable efforts to delete your information from our existing files.

When you do provide us with personally-identifiable information, we may use that information in the following ways, unless stated otherwise:

  * we may store and process that information to better understand all customer needs and how we can improve our products and services for all customers 
  * we may use that information to contact you with new promotions and announcements if you have previously provided your permission 
  * we may contact you if we have questions about your account 

Supertec will not sell personally-identifiable information to third parties, unless stated at the time of collection. We are committed to giving you the choice whether or not we use your information for marketing purposes or share information with business partners. 

**IV. Non-Personally-Identifiable Information Collected Automatically**  
In some cases, we may collect information about you that is not personally-identifiable. Examples of this type of information include the type of Internet Browser you are using, the type of computer operating system you are using, and the domain name of the Website and/or Internet Service Provider from which you linked to our site or advertisement.

Similar to personally identifiable information, we will not sell non-personally-identifiable information to third parties, unless stated at the time of collection. We may share non-personally identifiable information with business partners. 

**V. Use of Cookies**  
When you view one of our web sites or advertisements, we may store some information on your computer. This information will be in the form of a "Cookie" or similar file and will be used to determine ways to improve our web sites, advertisements, products or services. For example, cookies allow us to tailor a web site to better match your interests and preferences. With most Internet Browsers, you can erase Cookies from your computer hard drive, block all Cookies, or receive a warning before a Cookie is stored. Please refer to your browser instructions or help screen to learn more about these functions. 

**VI. Declining E-mail Offers**  
As outlined in Section III. of this Policy, we will only send email promotions or announcements to you if you have previously provided your permission for us to do so. Although many customers tell us they appreciate receiving notice of these carefully designed promotions and announcements, we recognize the importance of providing you with choices. At any time, you may unsubscribe from our e-mail list by filling out a simple online un-subscribe form. All e-mail offers that you receive from Supertec will inform you of how to decline receiving further email offers. 

**VII. Who to Contact**  
If you have submitted personally-identifiable information through a Supertec Web site or interactive advertisement, and would like that information deleted from our records, please contact us at our email address, care(at)supertec.com. We will use reasonable efforts to delete this information from our existing files.
